Class of 1907 Records, 1902-1977
Smith College Archives
Class of 1907 Records
1902-1977
Smith College. Class of 1907.
RG 80 UUID:452012d5-421d-4223-8b6a-9c07fdb067fd
20 boxes (13.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 20 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1907.
The Class of 1907 was the twenty-ninth entering class and the twenty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1907 records, 1902-1977, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1907, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1907 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Animal undated (Box 1703, Folder 1)
- Baccalaureate Service 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photos 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 5)
- Group Photos 1902-1907 (Box 1703, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1903 (Box 1703, Folder 7)
- Freshman Grind given by 1906 1903 (Box 1703, Folder 8)
- Freshman Frolic given by 1906 1903 (Box 1703, Folder 9)
- History undated (Box 1703, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day Photos 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom 1906 (Box 1703, Folder 13)
- Junior Prom Picnic 1906 (Box 1703, Folder 14)
- Junior Ushers 1906 (Box 1703, Folder 15)
- Class Letters 1917-1976 (Box 1703, Folder 16)
- Senior Dramatics 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics- Costume Design 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 4)
- Prize Song undated (Box 1704, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1908 (Box 1704, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1910 (Box 1704, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1912 (Box 1704, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1917 (Box 1704, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1927 (Box 1704, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1932 (Box 1704, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1937 (Box 1704, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 1704, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 1704, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 1704, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 1704, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 1704, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 1704, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 1704, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1977 (Box 1704, Folder 20)
- Songs undated (Box 1704, Folder 21)
- Sophomore Reception 1904 (Box 1704, Folder 22)
- Class Seal 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 23)
- Class Supper 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 24)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: A-B 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 1)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: C 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 2)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: D-F 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 3)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: G-H 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 4)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: J-L 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 5)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: M-N 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 6)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: O-P 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 7)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: R 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 8)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: S 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 9)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: T-V 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 10)
- 25th Reunion Questionnaires: W-Z 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 11)
- 30th Reunion Questionnaires: A-C 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 12)
- 30th Reunion Questionnaires: D-H 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 13)
- 30th Reunion Questionnaires: J-N 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 14)
- 30th Reunion Questionnaires: O-S 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 15)
- 30th Reunion Questionnaires: T-Z 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 16)
- Class Secretary's Book 1903-1937 (Box 1706, Folder 1)
- Register of the Class of 1907 1908-1962 (Box 1706, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Records 1907-1963 (Box 1706, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records 1907-1963 (Box 1706, Folder 4)
- Scrapbook 1928-1961 (Box 1706, Folder 5)